<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Against Violence to Overseas Chinese Women Program on AWDP</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/</link><description>Recent content in Against Violence to Overseas Chinese Women Program on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:41:03 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Background &amp; History</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/background/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:41:03 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/background/</guid><description>我们如何创建了AWDP？ Avoice (Against Violence to Overseas Chinese Women Program) is a youth-led NGO that aims to eliminate gender-based violence, advocate for gender equality, and assist Chinese migrant women facing domestic violence overseas. Avoice was launched in 2020 by the International Network of Young Volunteers, composed of Chinese university students and overseas Chinese students. Since 2020, we have attracted over 300 volunteers from 20+ countries with diverse backgrounds. Avoice has since partnered with 70 non-profit organizations and academic institutions that are concerned about female empowerment.</description></item><item><title>Our Motivation &amp; Goals</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/motivation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:41:03 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/motivation/</guid><description>Why AWDP? Avoice (Against Violence to Overseas Chinese Women Program) is a youth-led NGO that aims to eliminate gender-based violence, advocate for gender equality, and assist Chinese migrant women facing domestic violence overseas. Avoice was launched in 2020 by the International Network of Young Volunteers, composed of Chinese university students and overseas Chinese students. Since 2020, we have attracted over 300 volunteers from 20+ countries with diverse backgrounds. Avoice has since partnered with 70 non-profit organizations and academic institutions that are concerned about female empowerment.</description></item><item><title>我们是谁</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/who_are_we/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:41:03 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/zh-cn/about/who_are_we/</guid><description>Who are we? Avoice (Against Violence to Overseas Chinese Women Program) is a youth-led NGO that aims to eliminate gender-based violence, advocate for gender equality, and assist Chinese migrant women facing domestic violence overseas. Avoice was launched in 2020 by the International Network of Young Volunteers, composed of Chinese university students and overseas Chinese students. Since 2020, we have attracted over 300 volunteers from 20+ countries with diverse backgrounds. Avoice has since partnered with 70 non-profit organizations and academic institutions that are concerned about female empowerment.</description></item></channel></rss>