<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>美国 on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/tags/%E7%BE%8E%E5%9B%BD/</link><description>Recent content in 美国 on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/tags/%E7%BE%8E%E5%9B%BD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence and Support for Asian American Women After COVID-19</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</guid><description>Since the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic, domestic violence in the United States has become a &amp;ldquo;shadow problem&amp;rdquo; under the influence of the pandemic. Asian American women, who were already a relatively vulnerable group, have faced even more severe life-threatening crises. This article starts from the background of the post-pandemic era, focuses on the Asian American women who suffer from domestic violence in American society, and explores the survival status of the victimized Asian American women, as well as the assistance provided by the US government and society.</description></item><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence against Chinese American Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</guid><description>The article aims to review the existing literature with a comparative analysis of domestic violence against Chinese women and other ethnic groups in the United States. In this article, real portraits of the victims are presented to promote understanding of the specific dilemmas confronting Chinese American women， a horizontal comparison with white women and other minority women is conducted, and possible solutions are proposed to call for more attention to the sufferings from domestic violence against Chinese American women.</description></item></channel></rss>