<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/</link><description>Recent content in Home on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence and Support for Asian American Women After COVID-19</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</guid><description>Since the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic, domestic violence in the United States has become a &amp;ldquo;shadow problem&amp;rdquo; under the influence of the pandemic. Asian American women, who were already a relatively vulnerable group, have faced even more severe life-threatening crises. This article starts from the background of the post-pandemic era, focuses on the Asian American women who suffer from domestic violence in American society, and explores the survival status of the victimized Asian American women, as well as the assistance provided by the US government and society.</description></item><item><title>Special report on Indonesia - Current situation of Indonesian female migrant domestic workers</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_female_domestic_worker_report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_female_domestic_worker_report/</guid><description>This article presents a portrait of Indonesian female migrant domestic workers (not limited to Chinese women) through a scientific storytelling approach, mainly focusing on their current situation and looking forward to helping them in the future. The article uses UN reports, e-news and related documentaries as primary sources.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Until the gap in gender data is filled, please remain a "difficult" person——Invisible Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221226_invisible_women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221226_invisible_women/</guid><description>1. Introduction Despite accounting for half of the world’s population, women are still defined as a &amp;ldquo;gender minority&amp;rdquo; by the international community. Like the LGBTQ community, women are still under the constraints of systemic sexism and hidden exploitation despite existing ethics that promote tolerance and understanding. What&amp;rsquo;s even worse is that we&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to much of this oppression. We have been tricked by the kind facade of this sexism, and it has become an engrained restriction of ourselves.</description></item><item><title>The "Sleeping Bag Lady" - Don't Wallow in Sadness. Look Forward.</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221205_sleeping_bag_lady/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221205_sleeping_bag_lady/</guid><description>“&amp;ldquo;No one knows if love or violence came first.&amp;rdquo;
For her love of camping, she calls herself the &amp;ldquo;sleeping bag lady&amp;rdquo;.
Her mental grit and optimism kept her positive throughout the trials and tribulations of camping.
However, her life was full of other challenges, including the relentless physical abuse that she faced from her ex-boyfriend while studying alone in London. Facing this unexpected tribulation, the &amp;ldquo;sleeping bag lady&amp;rdquo; decided to grasp the nettle, call the police and seek punishment for her abuser as soon as possible, and move forward to a new life.</description></item><item><title>Self-Defense: Aegis of Women Against Domestic Violence</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221203_zeus_shield/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221203_zeus_shield/</guid><description>As an effective means of resisting domestic violence, the term “self-defense” often appears in the victim’s defense and the judicial court. But when violence strikes, blind self-defense could turn the victim to be the criminal, getting the vulnerable groups into the mire.
Therefore, before protecting ourselves from harm, we should all know how to walk a fine line on bravery and what is the bottom line of protection, so that “self-defense” can exert its maximum effectiveness within the law.</description></item><item><title>With the courage to follow one’s heart and an independent self, everyone can be an oasis</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221103_everyone_is_an_oasis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221103_everyone_is_an_oasis/</guid><description>Evelyn is a professional psychologist with knowledge of landscape architecture. She seems to be very special to have been given a mission to "save others" even before she was born. Although she experienced the struggle between reality and ideal on the way to growing up, fortunately, she still becomes a nourishing "oasis," literally like her name
When it comes to Evelyn, we'd rather call her "Oasis in the Desert." Evelyn had an artistic birth name, &amp;ldquo;Gezhou.</description></item><item><title>Women’s journey into the abyss is uncovered in this suspense novel.</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221013_girls_behind_suspense_novels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221013_girls_behind_suspense_novels/</guid><description>A book review of Scream &amp;ldquo;It was extraordinarily sunny on the day you were born, so your dad decided to name you Yoko!&amp;rdquo;
Yoko Suzuki is the protagonist of the novel Scream, written by Japanese novelist Aki Hamanaka. Born on a brilliantly sunny and cloudless day, she was therefore given the poetic name Yoko.
However, her name was actually casually decided by her parents. In the second baby boom, 2.</description></item><item><title>Distorted Relationships and Silent Aggression - "Odd Girl Out"</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221003_odd_girl_out/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221003_odd_girl_out/</guid><description>Abstract
Aggression in girls often emerges insidiously in intimate relationships, especially during adolescence, when girls are more likely to be sensitive and vulnerable. Aggression caused by abnormal social norms puts both the bully and the bullied in danger, and the distinct indirectness and elusiveness of this "alternative aggression" also makes it more difficult for schools and parents to intervene and respond. Under such circumstances, acknowledging the prevalence of violence among women and changing the public perception of this "</description></item><item><title>It's not about numbers: It is the stark reality of the lives of millions of women around the world</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220925_violence_behind_data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220925_violence_behind_data/</guid><description>Sixteen years ago, the UN General Assembly adopted a resolution calling for intensified efforts to eliminate all forms of violence against women and requested the Secretary-General of the UN to establish a database to illustrate the extent, nature, and consequences of violence against women and to explore the effectiveness of policy programmes to eliminate violence. In 2009, the database was officially developed and launched as the United Nations Secretary-General's Database on Violence against Women.</description></item><item><title>Vietnamese Brides：Vietnamese Women in Transnational Marriages</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Vietnamese brides&amp;rdquo; refer to Vietnamese women who migrate to other countries through arranged marriages, cross-border marriages, and mercenary marriages, taking marriage as a means to change their living conditions(薛瑛，2017). They account for a large population as an significant part of Vietnamese female immigrants. The transnational population movement of these women reflects the trend of transnational marriage and also implicates the economic gap among countries as well as the power relations between genders.</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume I)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</guid><description>This paper will take a close look at the harsh conditions of women in Afghanistan, a country of regime change and war, from three aspects: employment, education and physical rights. This paper（Volume I) will focus on the analysis and reflection of employment and education rights.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume II)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</guid><description>This paper discusses the implications of Muslim women&amp;rsquo;s wearing of veil within Muslim societies from the perspectives of religion, culture, socio-economic and political governance. The latter part of the paper takes France, Germany and the United States as examples to deeply explore the cultural conflicts and identity challenges faced by Muslim women as refugees or immigrants in secularized countries. The last part of the paper shows how Islamic women&amp;rsquo;s views and attitudes toward wearing the veil have changed over time.</description></item><item><title>Research on Domestic Violence against Chinese Women in Malaysia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</guid><description>As the Chinese community makes up an integral part of the Malaysian society, it is important that Malaysian Chinese women receive due attention to their lives and legitimate rights. This report focuses on the present situation of domestic violence against Chinese women in Malaysia, means of self-defense and social relief measures. Policies for local women’s rights and interests protection and laws on domestic violence are summarized to promote legal knowledge on the existing policies and means of self-defense, and provide ways to seek social aids.</description></item><item><title>Research report on domestic violence against women in Singapore</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</guid><description>According to the United Nations&amp;rsquo; Human Development Report, Singapore ranks 13th out of 155 countries and regions in gender equality, ranking first in Asia. However, the high gender equality rating does not mean that domestic violence against women in Singapore is not a serious problem. According to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Social and Family Development, from 2012 to 2016, domestic violence against women accounted for 74 to 76 percent of all cases, while domestic violence against men accounted for 24 to 25 percent during the same period.</description></item><item><title>Current situation and relief measures for domestic violence against women in the Philippines</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</guid><description>The Philippines has one of the highest domestic violence rates in the world. According to preliminary findings from the 2017 Philippine National Demographic and Health Survey (NDHS, 2018), about a quarter (26%) of married women aged 15-49 have experienced physical, sexual or emotional violence from their husband or partner. One in five women (20%) had experienced emotional violence, 14% had experienced physical violence and 5% had experienced sexual violence at the hands of a current or former husband or partner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of women's anti-domestic violence in Vietnam</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</guid><description>Domestic violence against women is widespread in Vietnam. Today, a significant proportion of women across the country continue to be at significant risk from intimate partner violence. Violence against women has had a serious negative impact on women&amp;rsquo;s health, safety, dignity and their potential to change their social status and their economic creativity. Violence against women in Vietnam is estimated to cause economic losses being equivalent to 1.8% of GDP. This paper will present and analyze the history and current situation of domestic violence in Vietnam, hoping that more attention and support can be put into the relief measures.</description></item><item><title>The Present Situation And Relief Measures of Domestic Violence Against Chinese Women in Indonesia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</guid><description>Being a widespread social problem, domestic violence is an unavoidable part of Indonesia’s current human rights issues. According to the report by the Central Indonesian National Committee, the situation exacerbates due to the prevailing COVID-19 pandemic. Data related show that 892 domestic violence cases were reported in Indonesia from January to May 2020, most of which were reported after the lock-down, while those unreported still lurk in every corner of Indonesian society.</description></item><item><title>Sally's Story of Chasing the Light</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</guid><description>Confronting the &amp;ldquo;scars&amp;rdquo; of the past and encouraging women to speak out together - Sally&amp;rsquo;s story of &amp;ldquo;chasing the light&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;For domestic violence, it is zero times or thousands of times.&amp;rdquo;
Everyone knows this saying, but few people can get out of the mire of domestic violence.
In this era featuring information overload, it is hard to believe there are few platforms that speak up for victims of domestic violence. We should pay more attention to how can victims of domestic violence face their diﬃculties, defend their rights and get out of the nightmare of domestic violence, especially when they have to take their families and friends into consideration and the public has stereotypes about Chinese women.</description></item><item><title>Soon 30, I Want to Become an Independently Standing Tree</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20211219_soon_30_independent_tree/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20211219_soon_30_independent_tree/</guid><description>Catherine
Catherine has lived in Australia all her life, from receiving her education to starting her own business to creating the "Around 30" podcast. Having experienced domestic violence, Catherine has experimented with numerous ways to heal and move past her trauma. Today, she lives triumphantly and freely in the realm of her independence. Raised in clamor and chaos to be a "people-pleaser"
&amp;ldquo;My parents have been strict with me since I was little, with my mother signing me up for several extra-curricular classes, pushing me academically, hoping I would get into a good college.</description></item><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence against Chinese American Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</guid><description>The article aims to review the existing literature with a comparative analysis of domestic violence against Chinese women and other ethnic groups in the United States. In this article, real portraits of the victims are presented to promote understanding of the specific dilemmas confronting Chinese American women， a horizontal comparison with white women and other minority women is conducted, and possible solutions are proposed to call for more attention to the sufferings from domestic violence against Chinese American women.</description></item><item><title>Observations on Global Anti-Domestic Violence Policies Released During the Pandemic</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</guid><description>Following the global outbreak of the COVID-19, &amp;ldquo;inequalities&amp;rdquo; in various forms become increasingly prominent in our society, domestic violence as one existing in family lives. &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo;, for many women and children in certain countries, is likewise considered a rather dangerous place amid the pandemic. The mounting severity of domestic violence is now drawing attention from both society and international organizations.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Aids &amp; Supports</title><link>https://awdpi.org/aids/get_support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/aids/get_support/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>