<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/</link><description>Recent content in Home on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The "Sleeping Bag Lady" - Don't Wallow in Sadness. Look Forward.</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221205_sleeping_bag_lady/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221205_sleeping_bag_lady/</guid><description>“&amp;ldquo;No one knows if love or violence came first.&amp;rdquo;
For her love of camping, she calls herself the &amp;ldquo;sleeping bag lady&amp;rdquo;.
Her mental grit and optimism kept her positive throughout the trials and tribulations of camping.
However, her life was full of other challenges, including the relentless physical abuse that she faced from her ex-boyfriend while studying alone in London. Facing this unexpected tribulation, the &amp;ldquo;sleeping bag lady&amp;rdquo; decided to grasp the nettle, call the police and seek punishment for her abuser as soon as possible, and move forward to a new life.</description></item><item><title>Avoice · 她视角｜扭曲的关系和沉默的攻击 ——《女孩们的地下战争》</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221003_odd_girl_out/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221003_odd_girl_out/</guid><description>摘要
女孩们之间的攻击以更为间接的形式藏匿于亲密关系之中，并且更多出现于敏感脆弱的青春期阶段。这种由于社会畸形规训而产生的攻击方式对霸凌者与被霸凌者来说，都是一种极具危险性的存在，而这一“另类攻击行为”特有的间接性与隐蔽性也使得学校的介入与家长的应对变得更加难以实现。在这一情况下，承认女性间暴力行为存在的普遍性，改变社会大众对这类“攻击文化”的认知，将有助于构筑一个更为友好与健康的女性成长环境。
“女孩发觉靠攻击性行为去争取权力是受到鼓励的。她们从未像如今这样承受着巨大的压力，被迫以损害自身健康发展的方式待人接物。” —— [美] 蕾切尔·西蒙斯 当我们谈论“针对女性的暴力行为”（Violence Against Women）时，我们是否已经默认施暴者是男性？一篇来自《北京社会科学》的研究报告 1 指出，根据联合国发布的《消除对妇女的暴力行为宣言》界定的概念，任何基于性别的对妇女的暴力行为都可称为“性别暴力”；换言之，女性对女性的暴力也应当被囊括于“VAW”的范畴中。然而事实上，有关女性之间的暴力行为的研究少之又少。
女性对女性的暴力行为，既包括直接的肢体冲突，也包括谣言、孤立、冷战以及数字时代特有的网络暴力等间接攻击，而后者的存在更为普遍。相比于男性“用拳头解决问题”的方式，女性之间的霸凌往往具有间接性和隐蔽性，也因此常常受到忽视，并且在某种意义上加剧了社会大众对女性的刻板印象（stereotype）。但是，我们应当深刻认识到——这种如瘟疫一般独特的攻击行为植根于社会对女性不合理的期待和假设，并且对施暴和受害者双方都具有残酷的毁灭性。
世界卫生组织在其针对女性暴力的研究中，将女性一生分为五个阶段：出生前，婴儿时期，少女时期，青春期，成人后和晚年。上述的霸凌行为在少女时期和青春期的女孩间尤为盛行，特别会出现在女孩所处的亲密关系和校园文化当中。
蕾切尔·西蒙斯（Rachel Simmons）经过数年在美国中小学的实地考察，通过给女孩授课，与女孩及她们的父母深入交谈，采访学校监管者、教师及辅导员等方式，进行素材与经验积累，最终完成了自己的专著《女孩们的地下战争：揭秘人际交往中的隐性攻击》（Odd Girl Out: The Hidden Culture of Aggression in Girls），探讨女孩间的隐性攻击存在的原因，以及这种畸形社交文化给她们带来的伤害。
“完美女孩”的亲密关系 女性间的亲密关系本身就是复杂的存在。学者卡萝尔·吉利根（Carol Gilligan）指出，关系与情感在女性生活中居于首要地位，因而相较男性，她们对损失有着更为强烈与敏感的反应。而女性间特有亲密关系的特质，也使更为隐秘的霸凌成为可能。西蒙斯也强调，女性之间的亲密指数，远高于男性与同性之间的指数。女性之间的友情，其亲密程度有时可与亲情媲美，甚至超过亲情的地位。但是，这一特征有时也会成为强有力的攻击点：作为最亲近的人，她们更懂得如何精准、致命地伤害到身边人。这种攻击行为难以识别，受害者的痛苦也会随着原本的亲密程度加剧。
1992年，一项研究揭示了女孩间特有的攻击方式，为社会提供了一扇一窥女孩之间非传统型愤怒表达方式的镜子。此后，明尼苏达大学（University of Minnesota）的心理学研究小组根据上述研究结果，将女孩的攻击行为分为三类：关系攻击、间接攻击和社交攻击。蕾切尔·西蒙斯将这些行为统称为“另类攻击行为”。
女性“不被允许”置身于公开的冲突中。“在这种文化中，”西蒙斯在书中写到，“文化通过定义‘友善’来剥夺女孩的权利：不能有攻击性，不能生气，不能发生正面冲突”。因此，女孩们往往被迫采取间接的、非肢体接触的方式展开攻击。比如，在“实话伤人”这一章节中，当面对“你对某人感到生气或不高兴时，会告诉她们吗”的问题时，绝大多数女孩表露出对于正面面对冲突的恐惧，她们认为“实话伤人，所以宁愿撒谎”。
亲密与危险之间的隔阂仅在毫厘之间。在社会刻板印象期待下，“完美女孩”应当拥有“完美关系”，当女孩期望拥有“完美女孩”、“好女孩”的光环时，她们在无形中也被剥夺了直面冲突、习得以成熟姿态解决亲密关系问题的机会。当女孩们决定“惩罚”自己的好友却不想显出“敌意”时，她们往往藏匿在甜美的面具下，转而进行悄无声息的伤害；而另一方，当被霸凌的女孩面对日复一日的残酷折磨时，对孤身一人的恐惧往往让她们甘愿维持一段施虐友谊。
在这一关于“完美女孩”的扭曲文化中，霸凌者可能丝毫意识不到自己的残酷，而被霸凌者则对不健康的友谊甘之如饴。女孩间特有的亲昵本应是她们感知复杂亲密关系的启蒙；但当表达愤怒的权利被污名化，性质不加检验的关系本身成为目的时，女孩们无法通过正常的情感交互与自我表达来妥善处理友情中存在的问题，而这最终无疑导向了一个个存在于亲密关系中的悲剧。
扭曲的“成人礼” 在西蒙斯看来，我们的社会存在着这样一种残酷的观念：女孩间的霸凌行为是她们长大成人必须学会的“过渡礼仪”，是女生都要经历的成长过程。这一观念使身处其中的孩子痛苦难耐，而父母、老师却毫无察觉。过渡礼仪论隐藏着这样几个令人不安的假设：首先，由于大量女孩都有过“另类攻击行为”，因此这一定是天性使然；其次，女孩们有必要学会以这种方式相处，为成年女性生活做铺垫；再次，既然女孩之间的刻薄是普遍存在、有所增益的，那么这就是她们在社会结构中的自然属性，应当被容忍，应当做好心理准备；最后，女孩之间的虐待其实根本就算不上虐待。这一观点及其暗含的假设让我们任由女孩子们在如履薄冰的校园环境中苦苦挣扎，仿佛我们只要在话语上把这一现象去问题化，就可以解除它为女孩子们带来的绝望与痛苦。
成长并不意味着一定要在逆境中重生，在绝望中反击，扭曲的“成人礼”可能只会让女孩子们提前感知并学会利用人性的残酷。遭受过校园霸凌的女孩，即便最终远离了那一让自己痛苦不堪的地方，曾遭受过的不解、不安、屈辱与渴望报复的狂热仍会鲜活地存在并不时浮现，这一痛苦永远不会随着时间逝去而消散。也正因如此，西蒙斯在此书后半部用了四章节的篇幅，探讨家长、老师以及作为学校管理者的成年人如何为处于成长期的女孩子提供正确的引导与帮助，尝试为孩子们提供一个真正的成人礼。
结语 西蒙斯倡导赋予女孩以协商化解冲突的能力。既然冲突是由对于失去关系恐惧引起的，那么女孩们应该被教导交朋友是一种选择，而不是强制命令。她们都有权利选择令自己舒服的关系。并且，如果友谊是一种选择，那么亲密和冲突都是正常现象。西蒙斯认为，如果女孩不再对失去关系充满恐惧，并相信真正的友谊经得起冲突的考量，她们将不再进行像“背后捅刀子”这样的隐性攻击行为。
“我希望她们，”西蒙斯在本书结尾写到，“以及任何一位当过落单女孩的女性，都能重新振作、大胆说出自己的想法，她们会低声自言自语：‘我最后悔的是当初保持沉默，到底有什么好怕的呢？’”
回到基于性别的对妇女的暴力行为，不难得出，不限于女性之间的友谊关系，在家暴发生的亲密关系当中，女性也都有权利选择令自己舒服的关系。友谊与亲密关系都需要经营，但经营绝不意味着毫无底线的退让，女性需要在有害关系经历中及时止损，勇敢走出暴力关系的操纵。
Avoice海外华人女性保护项目介绍链接： 作者 | 庞海尘 协作 | 马欣钰、桑宁敬 校改 | 符芬菊、吴思哲 审核 | 秦科 排版/封面 | 游舸 图片来源 | freepik 李鹏程，《女性之间的暴力：一种被忽视的性别暴力》，2016.06发表于《北京社会科学》。&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Vietnamese Brides：Vietnamese Women in Transnational Marriages</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Vietnamese brides&amp;rdquo; refer to Vietnamese women who migrate to other countries through arranged marriages, cross-border marriages, and mercenary marriages, taking marriage as a means to change their living conditions(薛瑛，2017). They account for a large population as an significant part of Vietnamese female immigrants. The transnational population movement of these women reflects the trend of transnational marriage and also implicates the economic gap among countries as well as the power relations between genders.</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume I)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</guid><description>This paper will take a close look at the harsh conditions of women in Afghanistan, a country of regime change and war, from three aspects: employment, education and physical rights. This paper（Volume I) will focus on the analysis and reflection of employment and education rights.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume II)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</guid><description>This paper discusses the implications of Muslim women&amp;rsquo;s wearing of veil within Muslim societies from the perspectives of religion, culture, socio-economic and political governance. The latter part of the paper takes France, Germany and the United States as examples to deeply explore the cultural conflicts and identity challenges faced by Muslim women as refugees or immigrants in secularized countries. The last part of the paper shows how Islamic women&amp;rsquo;s views and attitudes toward wearing the veil have changed over time.</description></item><item><title>Research on Domestic Violence against Chinese Women in Malaysia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</guid><description>As the Chinese community makes up an integral part of the Malaysian society, it is important that Malaysian Chinese women receive due attention to their lives and legitimate rights. This report focuses on the present situation of domestic violence against Chinese women in Malaysia, means of self-defense and social relief measures. Policies for local women’s rights and interests protection and laws on domestic violence are summarized to promote legal knowledge on the existing policies and means of self-defense, and provide ways to seek social aids.</description></item><item><title>Research report on domestic violence against women in Singapore</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</guid><description>According to the United Nations&amp;rsquo; Human Development Report, Singapore ranks 13th out of 155 countries and regions in gender equality, ranking first in Asia. However, the high gender equality rating does not mean that domestic violence against women in Singapore is not a serious problem. According to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Social and Family Development, from 2012 to 2016, domestic violence against women accounted for 74 to 76 percent of all cases, while domestic violence against men accounted for 24 to 25 percent during the same period.</description></item><item><title>Current situation and relief measures for domestic violence against women in the Philippines</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</guid><description>The Philippines has one of the highest domestic violence rates in the world. According to preliminary findings from the 2017 Philippine National Demographic and Health Survey (NDHS, 2018), about a quarter (26%) of married women aged 15-49 have experienced physical, sexual or emotional violence from their husband or partner. One in five women (20%) had experienced emotional violence, 14% had experienced physical violence and 5% had experienced sexual violence at the hands of a current or former husband or partner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of women's anti-domestic violence in Vietnam</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</guid><description>Domestic violence against women is widespread in Vietnam. Today, a significant proportion of women across the country continue to be at significant risk from intimate partner violence. Violence against women has had a serious negative impact on women&amp;rsquo;s health, safety, dignity and their potential to change their social status and their economic creativity. Violence against women in Vietnam is estimated to cause economic losses being equivalent to 1.8% of GDP. This paper will present and analyze the history and current situation of domestic violence in Vietnam, hoping that more attention and support can be put into the relief measures.</description></item><item><title>The Present Situation And Relief Measures of Domestic Violence Against Chinese Women in Indonesia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</guid><description>Being a widespread social problem, domestic violence is an unavoidable part of Indonesia’s current human rights issues. According to the report by the Central Indonesian National Committee, the situation exacerbates due to the prevailing COVID-19 pandemic. Data related show that 892 domestic violence cases were reported in Indonesia from January to May 2020, most of which were reported after the lock-down, while those unreported still lurk in every corner of Indonesian society.</description></item><item><title>Sally's Story of Chasing the Light</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</guid><description>Confronting the &amp;ldquo;scars&amp;rdquo; of the past and encouraging women to speak out together - Sally&amp;rsquo;s story of &amp;ldquo;chasing the light&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;For domestic violence, it is zero times or thousands of times.&amp;rdquo;
Everyone knows this saying, but few people can get out of the mire of domestic violence.
In this era featuring information overload, it is hard to believe there are few platforms that speak up for victims of domestic violence. We should pay more attention to how can victims of domestic violence face their diﬃculties, defend their rights and get out of the nightmare of domestic violence, especially when they have to take their families and friends into consideration and the public has stereotypes about Chinese women.</description></item><item><title>她视角｜数说暴力：数字背后，是全球无数女性赤裸裸的人生境遇</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220925_violence_behind_data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220925_violence_behind_data/</guid><description> 16年前，联合国大会通过了一项决议，呼吁加紧努力消除一切形式的暴力侵害妇女行为，并请联合国秘书长建立了一个数据库，以此说明暴力侵害妇女行为的程度、性质和后果，探讨消除暴力行为的政策方案所产生的影响和效力。2009年，这一数据库正式开发和启动，被称为“联合国秘书长关于暴力侵害妇女行为的数据库”。2016年，《2030年可持续发展议程》通过的背景下，联合国妇女署更新并重新设计了该数据库，并将其更名为“全球暴力侵害妇女问题全球数据库”。 图片来源：暴力侵害妇女问题全球数据库 呼吁建立暴力侵害妇女行为数据库的16年后，新冠疫情震荡了全球，压在女性身上的暴力行为在疫情背景下只增不减。世界卫生组织曾指出，亲密关系的暴力发生率会在灾难发生后普遍增加。新冠肺炎的肆虐激化了两性关系间的危机，此时此刻，家庭暴力的激增成为我们社会乃至整个世界不能忽视的问题。 凌虐不是爱，彰显霸权不是爱，无视矛盾也不是爱，在家庭暴力以及对女性的种种暴力行为背后，歧视与物化需要被发现，共情与同理心需要被呼吁，现状更需要被重视，并凝聚众人力量积极改变现状。 如何理解女性所经受的暴力，沉甸甸、实实在在的数据是最直观的、最全面的“窗口”之一。至今，全球已有多个数据库对暴力侵害妇女的行为进行了说明与印证。本期，Avoice将通过大数据，述说围绕全球女性的暴力行为，这些数据来自权威数据库，而数字的背后，则是无数女性赤裸裸的人生遭遇，是无数女性拼命挣扎，却难以逃离的泥淖。 冰冷的不是数字，是暴力 早在1993年，联合国就在大会第48/104号决议《消除对妇女的暴力行为宣言》中对“针对妇女的暴力行为（violence against women）”进行了概念界定，称其为 “对妇女造成或可能造成的身体、性或心理的伤害或痛苦的任何基于性别的暴力行为, 包括威胁、胁迫或任意剥夺自由, 无论其发生在公共还是私人生活中。”至今，针对女性的暴力行为仍无以计数……媒体曝光的只是冰山一角，数据库所记录的庞大数字背后，是难以想象的黑色世界和不忍触碰的层层伤疤。
01 性暴力：全球1/3妇女曾遭遇 2021年，联合国发布了完整版报告《针对妇女的暴力行为的2018年估计值》，这是联合国在2015-2030年可持续发展目标时期，调查访问全球137个国家及地区（包括41个高收入和96个中等收入、低收入国家及地区）的1266758位女性，首次针对妇女的暴力行为进行的估算。数据直观的印证，针对妇女的暴力行为仍然高发，如今，针对15岁及以上女性的暴力行为已是一个全球性、大规模流行的公共问题，影响到数以亿计的妇女。 图片来源：联合国妇女署公众号 该报告主要估计了亲密伴侣暴力和非伴侣性暴力两种类型的暴力。数据显示，亲密伴侣暴力，即丈夫或男性亲密伴侣的（身体、性或心理）暴力行为是全球最为普遍的针对妇女的暴力形式。 图片来源：联合国妇女署公众号 报告统计，在2018年约有7.36亿至8.52亿的15岁及以上的妇女（约占全球妇女人数1/3）终身至少经历过一次来自现任或前任丈夫或男性亲密伴侣的身体和/或性暴力或来自非伴侣的性暴力，如陌生人、熟人、朋友、同侪、老师、邻居、家庭成员或全部两种形式的暴力。此外，亲密伴侣暴力发生的时间较早，据估计，在15岁到19岁这一最年轻的年龄组中，几乎四分之一结过婚或有过伴侣的少女终身至少遭受过一次亲密伴侣的身体和/或性暴力，而且16%的15岁至24岁的少女和年轻妇女在过去12个月曾遭受过亲密伴侣暴力。 02 推攘、掌掴：1/5的欧盟女性曾遭受 在欧盟范围，欧盟曾于2014年3月，通过采访28个成员国的42000名妇女，统计这些女性曾遭受的身体暴力、性暴力、精神暴力情况和尾随跟踪、性骚扰的经历，发布了第一个针对妇女暴力的调查《针对妇女的暴力：一项欧盟范围内的调查》。 该调查显示，就非伴侣而言，每5名女性中就有1名（22%）曾经遭受过身体暴力，这些身体暴力的行为五花八门，如推攮、掌掴、被东西砸、被拽头发、被踢或用拳头击打、被烫伤、被掐或勒住脖子、被刺伤或割伤，以及被拽着头撞东西。 这些恐怖的身体暴力遭遇，往往并非一次，该数据显示，遭受过推攮的4,872名受访者中，约有19%的人曾遭受过6次或6次以上的暴力行为；遭受过掌掴的3,292名受访者中，曾有20%的人遭受过6次或6次以上的暴力行为。 03 后续追责：75%的男性未承担后果 调查表明，（亲密）伴侣暴力普遍存在，在有过伴侣的女性受访者中，39%报告了自己曾遭受过来自亲密伴侣的肢体暴力和/或性暴力。52%的男性受访者承认有过对亲密伴侣实施的暴力行为，而在曾强暴过女性的男性中，75％没有承担任何法律后果。 至于强暴动机，则以“性特权”——一种认为男性有权利与女性发生性关系，而无视女性同意或不同意的想法（86%）、找乐/无聊（58%）、生气/惩罚（43%）和喝了酒（24%）为主。 图片来源：搜信源 数据还显示，在所有受访男性中，73%认为男人应该强硬，52%支持男人使用暴力维护名誉；72%认为男性在家庭中应该是重要事情的决策者。这些所谓的“男性气质”和暴力行为有着紧密的关联。 此外，这份调查还显示，在曾实施过强暴的男性中，有67％在20岁到29岁时就实施了第一次强暴，有24％在15岁到19岁实施了第一次强暴，这些数据表明，预防性暴力和尊重女性的教育意识需要在青少年时期就开始。 看见暴力，消除暴力，爱无暴力 针对女性的暴力行为及不公正对待行为的权威数据远不仅此，在新冠疫情大流行期间的最新数据也亟待相关机构展开调查与研究。
根据联合国妇女署2022年最新数据，在新冠疫情下，除了面对更高几率的暴力行为，女性还面对着更难接种疫苗、更难获取食物，承担更多无偿照料和家务劳动、收入减少等境遇，多种境遇改变的数字背后，是每一位遭受暴力的女性个体流下的泪水。
在世界、在全球，对女性的暴力依旧存在，媒体上有关家暴等的议题仍层出不穷，世界对女性不合理的体制仍旧存在，如何真正“看见”女性、及时有效的帮助女性，仍然任重道远。
就像开头所说，凌虐不是爱，彰显霸权不是爱，无视矛盾也不是爱，我们需要建立一个无暴力、有同理心、真正平等的爱的共同体。《女性与权力》一书中，玛尔·比尔德写到，“你无法将女性轻易置于一个已经被男性化编码的架构里，你必须改变架构本身。”我们期待一个爱无暴力的世界的到来，愿Avoice和你，都能成为照亮这个世界的“光”。
参考文献
联合国妇女署公众号《来自联合国，最新版 “针对妇女的暴力行为全球流行率估计”报告发布！》 https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/O285OYtko4nEBtLRDb6CNA 欧盟《针对妇女的暴力：一项欧盟范围内的调查》 https://fra.europa.eu/sites/default/files/fra_uploads/fra-2014-vaw-survey-main-results-apr14_en.pdf 全球暴力侵害妇女问题全球数据库 https://evaw-global-database.unwomen.org/en 第四期中国妇女社会地位调查主要数据情况发布，中国妇女研究网 (wsic.ac.cn) 联合国妇女署官网 搜新源公众号《并非男性都是施暴者，但是女性都生活在系统性恐惧中 | 搜信源》 Avoice海外华人女性保护项目作为华人女性坚实温暖的后盾，为Sally提供后续的咨询和帮助。 同时，Sally也成为了Avoice的志愿者，在我们的线上华人女性社群中，为其他女性提供一对一的咨询，并且将她的经验和能量传递给其他需要帮助的华人女性。 Avoice海外华人女性保护项目介绍链接： 作者 | 秦科 审核 | Jane 排版 | 圆圆</description></item><item><title>Soon 30, I Want to Become an Independently Standing Tree</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20211219_soon_30_independent_tree/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20211219_soon_30_independent_tree/</guid><description>Catherine
Catherine has lived in Australia all her life, from receiving her education to starting her own business to creating the "Around 30" podcast. Having experienced domestic violence, Catherine has experimented with numerous ways to heal and move past her trauma. Today, she lives triumphantly and freely in the realm of her independence. Raised in clamor and chaos to be a "people-pleaser"
&amp;ldquo;My parents have been strict with me since I was little, with my mother signing me up for several extra-curricular classes, pushing me academically, hoping I would get into a good college.</description></item><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence against Chinese American Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</guid><description>The article aims to review the existing literature with a comparative analysis of domestic violence against Chinese women and other ethnic groups in the United States. In this article, real portraits of the victims are presented to promote understanding of the specific dilemmas confronting Chinese American women， a horizontal comparison with white women and other minority women is conducted, and possible solutions are proposed to call for more attention to the sufferings from domestic violence against Chinese American women.</description></item><item><title>Observations on Global Anti-Domestic Violence Policies Released During the Pandemic</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</guid><description>Following the global outbreak of the COVID-19, &amp;ldquo;inequalities&amp;rdquo; in various forms become increasingly prominent in our society, domestic violence as one existing in family lives. &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo;, for many women and children in certain countries, is likewise considered a rather dangerous place amid the pandemic. The mounting severity of domestic violence is now drawing attention from both society and international organizations.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Aids &amp; Supports</title><link>https://awdpi.org/aids/get_support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/aids/get_support/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>