<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Research on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/</link><description>Recent content in Research on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:41:03 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence against Chinese American Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report_post_covid/</guid><description>Since the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic, domestic violence in the United States has become a &amp;ldquo;shadow problem&amp;rdquo; under the influence of the pandemic. Asian American women, who were already a relatively vulnerable group, have faced even more severe life-threatening crises. This article starts from the background of the post-pandemic era, focuses on the Asian American women who suffer from domestic violence in American society, and explores the survival status of the victimized Asian American women, as well as the assistance provided by the US government and society.</description></item><item><title>Special report on Indonesia - Current situation of Indonesian female migrant domestic workers</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_female_domestic_worker_report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_female_domestic_worker_report/</guid><description>This article presents a portrait of Indonesian female migrant domestic workers (not limited to Chinese women) through a scientific storytelling approach, mainly focusing on their current situation and looking forward to helping them in the future. The article uses UN reports, e-news and related documentaries as primary sources.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Vietnamese Brides：Vietnamese Women in Transnational Marriages</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Vietnamese brides&amp;rdquo; refer to Vietnamese women who migrate to other countries through arranged marriages, cross-border marriages, and mercenary marriages, taking marriage as a means to change their living conditions(薛瑛，2017). They account for a large population as an significant part of Vietnamese female immigrants. The transnational population movement of these women reflects the trend of transnational marriage and also implicates the economic gap among countries as well as the power relations between genders.</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume I)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</guid><description>This paper will take a close look at the harsh conditions of women in Afghanistan, a country of regime change and war, from three aspects: employment, education and physical rights. This paper（Volume I) will focus on the analysis and reflection of employment and education rights.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume II)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</guid><description>This paper discusses the implications of Muslim women&amp;rsquo;s wearing of veil within Muslim societies from the perspectives of religion, culture, socio-economic and political governance. The latter part of the paper takes France, Germany and the United States as examples to deeply explore the cultural conflicts and identity challenges faced by Muslim women as refugees or immigrants in secularized countries. The last part of the paper shows how Islamic women&amp;rsquo;s views and attitudes toward wearing the veil have changed over time.</description></item><item><title>Research on Domestic Violence against Chinese Women in Malaysia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/mys_report/</guid><description>As the Chinese community makes up an integral part of the Malaysian society, it is important that Malaysian Chinese women receive due attention to their lives and legitimate rights. This report focuses on the present situation of domestic violence against Chinese women in Malaysia, means of self-defense and social relief measures. Policies for local women’s rights and interests protection and laws on domestic violence are summarized to promote legal knowledge on the existing policies and means of self-defense, and provide ways to seek social aids.</description></item><item><title>Research report on domestic violence against women in Singapore</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/sgp_report/</guid><description>According to the United Nations&amp;rsquo; Human Development Report, Singapore ranks 13th out of 155 countries and regions in gender equality, ranking first in Asia. However, the high gender equality rating does not mean that domestic violence against women in Singapore is not a serious problem. According to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Social and Family Development, from 2012 to 2016, domestic violence against women accounted for 74 to 76 percent of all cases, while domestic violence against men accounted for 24 to 25 percent during the same period.</description></item><item><title>Current situation and relief measures for domestic violence against women in the Philippines</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/phl_report/</guid><description>The Philippines has one of the highest domestic violence rates in the world. According to preliminary findings from the 2017 Philippine National Demographic and Health Survey (NDHS, 2018), about a quarter (26%) of married women aged 15-49 have experienced physical, sexual or emotional violence from their husband or partner. One in five women (20%) had experienced emotional violence, 14% had experienced physical violence and 5% had experienced sexual violence at the hands of a current or former husband or partner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of women's anti-domestic violence in Vietnam</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</guid><description>Domestic violence against women is widespread in Vietnam. Today, a significant proportion of women across the country continue to be at significant risk from intimate partner violence. Violence against women has had a serious negative impact on women&amp;rsquo;s health, safety, dignity and their potential to change their social status and their economic creativity. Violence against women in Vietnam is estimated to cause economic losses being equivalent to 1.8% of GDP. This paper will present and analyze the history and current situation of domestic violence in Vietnam, hoping that more attention and support can be put into the relief measures.</description></item><item><title>The Present Situation And Relief Measures of Domestic Violence Against Chinese Women in Indonesia</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/idn_report/</guid><description>Being a widespread social problem, domestic violence is an unavoidable part of Indonesia’s current human rights issues. According to the report by the Central Indonesian National Committee, the situation exacerbates due to the prevailing COVID-19 pandemic. Data related show that 892 domestic violence cases were reported in Indonesia from January to May 2020, most of which were reported after the lock-down, while those unreported still lurk in every corner of Indonesian society.</description></item><item><title>Report on Domestic Violence against Chinese American Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/us_report/</guid><description>The article aims to review the existing literature with a comparative analysis of domestic violence against Chinese women and other ethnic groups in the United States. In this article, real portraits of the victims are presented to promote understanding of the specific dilemmas confronting Chinese American women， a horizontal comparison with white women and other minority women is conducted, and possible solutions are proposed to call for more attention to the sufferings from domestic violence against Chinese American women.</description></item><item><title>Observations on Global Anti-Domestic Violence Policies Released During the Pandemic</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/multiple_countries/</guid><description>Following the global outbreak of the COVID-19, &amp;ldquo;inequalities&amp;rdquo; in various forms become increasingly prominent in our society, domestic violence as one existing in family lives. &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo;, for many women and children in certain countries, is likewise considered a rather dangerous place amid the pandemic. The mounting severity of domestic violence is now drawing attention from both society and international organizations.
Download Report</description></item></channel></rss>