<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fairy tales on Avoice</title><link>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/tags/fairy-tales/</link><description>Recent content in fairy tales on Avoice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 21:48:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/tags/fairy-tales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alice</title><link>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/alice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 21:48:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/alice/</guid><description>The King and Queen of Hearts were seated on their throne when they arrived, with a great crowd assembled about them—all sorts of little birds and beasts, as well as the whole pack of cards: the Knave was standing before them, in chains, with a soldier on each side to guard him; and near the King was the White Rabbit, with a trumpet in one hand, and a scroll of parchment in the other.</description></item><item><title>The Elves and the Shoemaker</title><link>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/the-elves-and-the-shoemaker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 06:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/the-elves-and-the-shoemaker/</guid><description>There was once a shoemaker, who worked very hard and was very honest: but still he could not earn enough to live upon; and at last all he had in the world was gone, save just leather enough to make one pair of shoes.
Then he cut his leather out, all ready to make up the next day, meaning to rise early in the morning to his work. His conscience was clear and his heart light amidst all his troubles; so he went peaceably to bed, left all his cares to Heaven, and soon fell asleep.</description></item><item><title>The Raven</title><link>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/the-raven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 11:07:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/the-raven/</guid><description>There was once a queen who had a little daughter, still too young to run alone. One day the child was very troublesome, and the mother could not quiet it, do what she would. She grew impatient, and seeing the ravens flying round the castle, she opened the window, and said: ‘I wish you were a raven and would fly away, then I should have a little peace.’ Scarcely were the words out of her mouth, when the child in her arms was turned into a raven, and flew away from her through the open window.</description></item><item><title>Doctor Knowall</title><link>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/doctor-knowall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 23:21:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cohub-hugo.netlify.app/post/doctor-knowall/</guid><description>There was once upon a time a poor peasant called Crabb, who drove with two oxen a load of wood to the town, and sold it to a doctor for two talers. When the money was being counted out to him, it so happened that the doctor was sitting at table, and when the peasant saw how well he ate and drank, his heart desired what he saw, and would willingly have been a doctor too.</description></item></channel></rss>