<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>阿富汗 on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/tags/%E9%98%BF%E5%AF%8C%E6%B1%97/</link><description>Recent content in 阿富汗 on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/tags/%E9%98%BF%E5%AF%8C%E6%B1%97/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume I)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_1/</guid><description>This paper will take a close look at the harsh conditions of women in Afghanistan, a country of regime change and war, from three aspects: employment, education and physical rights. This paper（Volume I) will focus on the analysis and reflection of employment and education rights.
Download Report</description></item><item><title>Protection of Women's Rights and Interests in Turbulent Countries -- A Case Study of Afghanistan (Volume II)</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/afg_report_2/</guid><description>This paper discusses the implications of Muslim women&amp;rsquo;s wearing of veil within Muslim societies from the perspectives of religion, culture, socio-economic and political governance. The latter part of the paper takes France, Germany and the United States as examples to deeply explore the cultural conflicts and identity challenges faced by Muslim women as refugees or immigrants in secularized countries. The last part of the paper shows how Islamic women&amp;rsquo;s views and attitudes toward wearing the veil have changed over time.</description></item></channel></rss>