<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>novels on Avoice</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/tags/novels/</link><description>Recent content in novels on Avoice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 15:31:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdp-avoice.github.io/tags/novels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Holmes</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/post/holmes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 15:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/post/holmes/</guid><description>At three o’clock precisely I was at Baker Street, but Holmes had not yet returned. The landlady informed me that he had left the house shortly after eight o’clock in the morning. I sat down beside the fire, however, with the intention of awaiting him, however long he might be. I was already deeply interested in his inquiry, for, though it was surrounded by none of the grim and strange features which were associated with the two crimes which I have already recorded, still, the nature of the case and the exalted station of his client gave it a character of its own.</description></item><item><title>Great Expectations</title><link>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/post/great-expectations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 17:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdp-avoice.github.io/post/great-expectations/</guid><description>In vain should I attempt to describe the astonishment and disquiet of Herbert, when he and I and Provis sat down before the fire, and I recounted the whole of the secret. Enough, that I saw my own feelings reflected in Herbert’s face, and not least among them, my repugnance towards the man who had done so much for me.
What would alone have set a division between that man and us, if there had been no other dividing circumstance, was his triumph in my story.</description></item></channel></rss>