<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>越南 on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/tags/%E8%B6%8A%E5%8D%97/</link><description>Recent content in 越南 on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/tags/%E8%B6%8A%E5%8D%97/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vietnamese Brides：Vietnamese Women in Transnational Marriages</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vietnamese_brides/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Vietnamese brides&amp;rdquo; refer to Vietnamese women who migrate to other countries through arranged marriages, cross-border marriages, and mercenary marriages, taking marriage as a means to change their living conditions(薛瑛，2017). They account for a large population as an significant part of Vietnamese female immigrants. The transnational population movement of these women reflects the trend of transnational marriage and also implicates the economic gap among countries as well as the power relations between genders.</description></item><item><title>Overview of women's anti-domestic violence in Vietnam</title><link>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/research/vnm_report/</guid><description>Domestic violence against women is widespread in Vietnam. Today, a significant proportion of women across the country continue to be at significant risk from intimate partner violence. Violence against women has had a serious negative impact on women&amp;rsquo;s health, safety, dignity and their potential to change their social status and their economic creativity. Violence against women in Vietnam is estimated to cause economic losses being equivalent to 1.8% of GDP. This paper will present and analyze the history and current situation of domestic violence in Vietnam, hoping that more attention and support can be put into the relief measures.</description></item></channel></rss>