<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>她视角 on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/tags/%E5%A5%B9%E8%A7%86%E8%A7%92/</link><description>Recent content in 她视角 on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/tags/%E5%A5%B9%E8%A7%86%E8%A7%92/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Until the gap in gender data is filled, please remain a "difficult" person——Invisible Women</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221226_invisible_women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221226_invisible_women/</guid><description>1. Introduction Despite accounting for half of the world’s population, women are still defined as a &amp;ldquo;gender minority&amp;rdquo; by the international community. Like the LGBTQ community, women are still under the constraints of systemic sexism and hidden exploitation despite existing ethics that promote tolerance and understanding. What&amp;rsquo;s even worse is that we&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to much of this oppression. We have been tricked by the kind facade of this sexism, and it has become an engrained restriction of ourselves.</description></item><item><title>Self-Defense: Aegis of Women Against Domestic Violence</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221203_zeus_shield/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221203_zeus_shield/</guid><description>As an effective means of resisting domestic violence, the term “self-defense” often appears in the victim’s defense and the judicial court. But when violence strikes, blind self-defense could turn the victim to be the criminal, getting the vulnerable groups into the mire.
Therefore, before protecting ourselves from harm, we should all know how to walk a fine line on bravery and what is the bottom line of protection, so that “self-defense” can exert its maximum effectiveness within the law.</description></item></channel></rss>