<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>愈见·她说 on AWDP</title><link>https://awdpi.org/tags/%E6%84%88%E8%A7%81%E5%A5%B9%E8%AF%B4/</link><description>Recent content in 愈见·她说 on AWDP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awdpi.org/tags/%E6%84%88%E8%A7%81%E5%A5%B9%E8%AF%B4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sally's Story of Chasing the Light</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20220103_sallys_story_of_chasing_the_light/</guid><description>Confronting the &amp;ldquo;scars&amp;rdquo; of the past and encouraging women to speak out together - Sally&amp;rsquo;s story of &amp;ldquo;chasing the light&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;For domestic violence, it is zero times or thousands of times.&amp;rdquo;
Everyone knows this saying, but few people can get out of the mire of domestic violence.
In this era featuring information overload, it is hard to believe there are few platforms that speak up for victims of domestic violence. We should pay more attention to how can victims of domestic violence face their diﬃculties, defend their rights and get out of the nightmare of domestic violence, especially when they have to take their families and friends into consideration and the public has stereotypes about Chinese women.</description></item><item><title>Soon 30, I Want to Become an Independently Standing Tree</title><link>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221219_soon_30_independent_tree/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awdpi.org/stories/20221219_soon_30_independent_tree/</guid><description>Catherine
Catherine has lived in Australia all her life, from receiving her education to starting her own business to creating the "Around 30" podcast. Having experienced domestic violence, Catherine has experimented with numerous ways to heal and move past her trauma. Today, she lives triumphantly and freely in the realm of her independence. Raised in clamor and chaos to be a "people-pleaser"
&amp;ldquo;My parents have been strict with me since I was little, with my mother signing me up for several extra-curricular classes, pushing me academically, hoping I would get into a good college.</description></item></channel></rss>